Derick Fabert

Full Stack Web Developer
Mooresville, IN 46158

(317) 258-0021 glen.fabert@gmail.com github.com/dfabert www.linkedin.com/in/derick-fabert/ dfabert.github.io/Derick Fabert

Education

Butler University

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development *December 2020*

Purdue University

Bachelor of Science, Meteorology August 2007

Skills

- HTML5, CSS, React.js
- JavaScript, jQuery, ES6+
- GIT, Bootstrap, AJAX, Handlebars
- Node, Express, MySql
- Team member development
- Client relations
- Certified Broadcast Meteorologist,
 American Meteorological Society

Recognition

- 2015 Silver Dome Award Best Use of Interactive Media
- 2014 Silver Dome Award

 Best TV
 Weathercaster

Profile

Full stack web developer with experience in management, broadcast meteorology and real estate. Recent graduate of Butler's Web Development Bootcamp and previously received a Bachelor of Science in meteorology from Purdue University. Experience includes leadership roles and development of a weather focused website. Successfully led a weather and news team through several severe weather events, including tornadoes, blizzards, and floods. Passionate about client relations, accuracy and safety. Delighted to be returning to the web development world to solve complex problems using my new and old skills in a fast-paced environment.

Experience

Future Wonder, Bloomington, IN

May 2021 – Present, Junior Development Consultant Develop UI components using React.js, CSS for a financial industry client specializing in cryptocurrency. Collaborate with server-side developers to maximize speed of development.

Adams/Fairway/Reagan Outdoor Advertising, Indianapolis, IN

April 2017 – May 2021, Real Estate Manager/Representative Effectively oversaw new build projects from start to finish, searched zoning maps and property for potential areas of growth, and successfully cultivated and fostered relationships with lessors. Maintained responsibilities through a corporate transition in ownership after transferring from a smaller regional office in Illinois (Adams Outdoor Advertising).

WCIA (CBS), Champaign, IL

April 2010 - April 2017, Chief Meteorologist
Led the weather team and general weather product for news,
managed high-stress situations (including severe weather and
breaking news), and developed and maintained the weather
website. Awarded "most accurate weather team" five straight
years.